<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on n.b.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on n.b.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Web Browsing in 2025: Beyond Traditional Browsers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/zen-folders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/zen-folders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Browser Revolution of 2025: How We&amp;rsquo;re Reimagining Web Navigation&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t remember the last time I was this excited about browsers. Seriously! For years, we&amp;rsquo;ve been stuck in this rut where Chrome, Safari, Firefox, and Edge just kept adding bells and whistles without actually rethinking what a browser should be. But 2025 feels different, like we&amp;rsquo;re finally breaking out of old habits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/arc&#34;&gt;moving from Chrome to Arc&lt;/a&gt; and then &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/zen&#34;&gt;switching to Zen&lt;/a&gt;, I&amp;rsquo;ve had front-row seats to this quiet revolution. It&amp;rsquo;s like watching the early days of smartphones all over again, that moment when we realized phones could be so much more than just&amp;hellip; phones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing, Even When It’s Cool</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/change/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/change/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some jobs are easy to leave. And then there are those where every day teaches you something, where the team is brilliant, funny, professional, where even barbecuing is part of the culture. Leaving that? Not so easy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I spent 7 incredible years at QoQa, learning, growing, failing, trying again—always with this wild freedom to explore, to break things (sometimes on purpose), and yes, to grill. I had the chance to work with truly talented people. I’m deeply grateful for that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m Leaving Arc: The Browser That Redefined My Web Experience (But Might Be Losing Its Way)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/zen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/zen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Arc is brilliant but its future feels uncertain, so I&amp;rsquo;m moving to Zen Browser, a Firefox-based alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I&amp;rsquo;m Leaving Arc: The Browser That Redefined My Web Experience (But Might Be Losing Its Way)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2022, I made a pivotal change in my digital habits: I &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/arc&#34;&gt;left Google Chrome for Arc Browser&lt;/a&gt;. Arc wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a new browser, it was a breath of fresh air in a landscape dominated by stagnant design and functionality. For a while, it felt like the future of web navigation was unfolding right before me. But now, as 2025 begins, I find myself reconsidering my choice, not because Arc isn&amp;rsquo;t great, but because its future feels uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Finding My Family&#39;s Coat of Arms Connected Me With My Roots</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/herald/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt;: Finding family coat of arms is fun, espacially in Vaud Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;when-ancient-symbols-became-personal-my-familys-heraldry-journey&#34;&gt;When Ancient Symbols Became Personal: My Family&amp;rsquo;s Heraldry Journey&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few years ago, if someone had told me I&amp;rsquo;d have my family&amp;rsquo;s coat of arms tattooed on my body, I probably would have laughed. Yet here I am today, proudly wearing these ancient symbols that represent centuries of family history. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing how a simple visit to the Vaud Cantonal Archives turned into a life-changing journey of discovery.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTD: My Life became a todo list</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gtd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt;: GTD (Getting Things Done) is more than just a productivity system - it&amp;rsquo;s a lifestyle change&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few years ago, if someone had told me I&amp;rsquo;d become a die-hard GTD enthusiast, I probably would have smiled politely. Yet here I am today, navigating the sometimes turbulent but always enriching waters of organized productivity. It&amp;rsquo;s as if my former self, drowning in post-its and incomplete to-do lists, had finally found a compass in the ocean of daily chaos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QoQa Beta, The Core of the QoQa Community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/qoqabeta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/qoqabeta/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Discover the behind-the-scenes world of beta testing through the story of a manager overseeing 800 testers. From daily challenges to the importance of human contact and strategies for maintaining engagement, this text offers a unique glimpse into a realm where every contribution can shape the future of technological innovations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A couple years ago, if someone had told me I&amp;rsquo;d be leading a pool of beta testers, I probably would have laughed. Yet here I am today, navigating the sometimes turbulent but always exciting waters of beta testing. It&amp;rsquo;s as if my curious child self, the one who used to take apart toys to understand how they worked, had grown up to become the guardian of a community of 800 digital explorers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to school</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/etml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/etml/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ten years ago, I left &lt;a href=&#34;http://etml.ch/formation/es/informatique-de-gestion&#34;&gt;ETML-ES&lt;/a&gt; with my diploma in hand, and last June 25th, I had the chance to go back in time by returning to my old school. It was nice to see the places and meet the final year students.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I prepared for my presentation, I wondered how I could talk about myself while also talking about them. A difficult exercise, because I must admit that I was never a huge fan of academic learning, and I was far from being the best student in the class. Even worse: I haven&amp;rsquo;t coded in years and I practice a profession that wasn&amp;rsquo;t even mentioned during my studies. So, drawing from these past 10 years, I tried to propose a &amp;ldquo;cheat sheet&amp;rdquo;, a crib sheet, that could help them avoid the missteps I made.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of a Personal Website and my Struggle to Find the Right One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/swiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/swiss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a test manager, I understand the value of having a personal portfolio website to showcase my skills and experience. However, the process of creating a website that I was truly happy with took me 15 years and 18 different versions. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my journey and the lessons I&amp;rsquo;ve learned about the importance of a personal website and the struggle to find the right technology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-struggle-to-find-the-right-technology&#34;&gt;The Struggle to Find the Right Technology&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest challenges I faced was finding the right technology to build my website. I experimented with various content management systems, such as WordPress, but found them to be too bloated and slow for my needs. That&amp;rsquo;s why I eventually settled on using Hugo, a static site generator that allows me to create a fast and efficient website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGR: An Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dgr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dgr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every year, the Gentleman&amp;rsquo;s Ride holds a special place in my heart and my life. This year marks my sixth participation in this iconic event, and I&amp;rsquo;m more excited than ever to share what it represents to me, the causes it fights for, and why it&amp;rsquo;s so special.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Gentleman&amp;rsquo;s Ride is more than just a motorcycle ride. It&amp;rsquo;s a global initiative aimed at raising awareness and funds for prostate cancer research and men&amp;rsquo;s mental health. The statistics are alarming: men die on average six years earlier than women, often for preventable reasons. That&amp;rsquo;s why this event is so crucial. Participating in this ride means contributing to a global movement striving to improve men&amp;rsquo;s health and well-being everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I ditched Chrome, And why you should too.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/arc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Embracing a New Chapter: My Transition from Chrome to Arc Browser&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2022, while reading about self-driving cars, my phone rang. It was a buddy excited about manned missions to Mars. As I glanced at my Mac and opened Chrome to learn more, I realized: everything around us is evolving rapidly, except our web browsers. They&amp;rsquo;ve remained almost the same for ages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That was the moment I decided to change. Why stick with an old-school browser when everything else is transforming? That&amp;rsquo;s when I decided to give &lt;a href=&#34;https://arc.net?source=nathan.swiss&#34;&gt;Arc Browser&lt;/a&gt; a shot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Curiosity to Quality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/qa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Although nowadays, careers related to computer science are highly sought after, I must admit that it was not at all my initial ambition. Yet, the winding path that led me to become a software tester is a beautiful testament to the power of curiosity and perseverance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From a very young age, I have always been a passionate and curious child about everything. Each new toy quickly became an object of thorough investigation. I wanted to understand how it worked, what were its mechanisms. Very often, my parents would find me in the middle of disassembled pieces, which I rarely put back together, by the way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
