<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nathan Buache</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nathan Buache</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright> - © NB</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Based in Lausanne 🇨🇭, I work at QoQa, a company fueled by fun and craziness. As a Test Manager, my role is to ensure that websites and applications function as they should. With 7 years of experience in the QA field, I am known for being open, a bit crazy, and efficient in my work.&#xA;I am a trained IT management technician who has turned my passion into my profession: I do what I love and love what I do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Sixth Participation in the Gentleman&#39;s Ride: An Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-4/</guid>
      <description>Every year, the Gentleman&amp;rsquo;s Ride holds a special place in my heart and my life. This year marks my sixth participation in this iconic event, and I&amp;rsquo;m more excited than ever to share what it represents to me, the causes it fights for, and why it&amp;rsquo;s so special.&#xA;The Gentleman&amp;rsquo;s Ride is more than just a motorcycle ride. It&amp;rsquo;s a global initiative aimed at raising awareness and funds for prostate cancer research and men&amp;rsquo;s mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I ditched Google Chrome, And why you should too.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Embracing a New Chapter: My Transition from Chrome to Arc Browser At the end of 2022, while reading about self-driving cars, my phone rang. It was a buddy excited about manned missions to Mars. As I glanced at my Mac and opened Chrome to learn more, I realized: everything around us is evolving rapidly, except our web browsers. They’ve remained almost the same for ages.&#xA;That was the moment I decided to change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Curiosity to Quality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post-5/</guid>
      <description>Although nowadays, careers related to computer science are highly sought after, I must admit that it was not at all my initial ambition. Yet, the winding path that led me to become a software tester is a beautiful testament to the power of curiosity and perseverance.&#xA;From a very young age, I have always been a passionate and curious child about everything. Each new toy quickly became an object of thorough investigation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
