<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome! on Nathan Buache</title>
    <link>https://nathan.swiss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome! on Nathan Buache</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:15:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nathan.swiss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Finding My Family&#39;s Coat of Arms Connected Me With My Roots</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/herald/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: Finding family coat of arms is fun, espacially in Vaud Switzerland.&#xA;When Ancient Symbols Became Personal: My Family&amp;rsquo;s Heraldry Journey A few years ago, if someone had told me I&amp;rsquo;d have my family&amp;rsquo;s coat of arms tattooed on my body, I probably would have laughed. Yet here I am today, proudly wearing these ancient symbols that represent centuries of family history. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing how a simple visit to the Vaud Cantonal Archives turned into a life-changing journey of discovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTD: My Life became a todo list</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/gtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/gtd/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: GTD (Getting Things Done) is more than just a productivity system - it&amp;rsquo;s a lifestyle change&#xA;A few years ago, if someone had told me I&amp;rsquo;d become a die-hard GTD enthusiast, I probably would have smiled politely. Yet here I am today, navigating the sometimes turbulent but always enriching waters of organized productivity. It&amp;rsquo;s as if my former self, drowning in post-its and incomplete to-do lists, had finally found a compass in the ocean of daily chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QoQa Beta, The Core of the QoQa Community</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/qoqabeta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/qoqabeta/</guid>
      <description>Discover the behind-the-scenes world of beta testing through the story of a manager overseeing 800 testers. From daily challenges to the importance of human contact and strategies for maintaining engagement, this text offers a unique glimpse into a realm where every contribution can shape the future of technological innovations.&#xA;A couple years ago, if someone had told me I&amp;rsquo;d be leading a pool of beta testers, I probably would have laughed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to school</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/etml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/etml/</guid>
      <description>Ten years ago, I left ETML-ES with my diploma in hand, and last June 25th, I had the chance to go back in time by returning to my old school. It was nice to see the places and meet the final year students.&#xA;As I prepared for my presentation, I wondered how I could talk about myself while also talking about them. A difficult exercise, because I must admit that I was never a huge fan of academic learning, and I was far from being the best student in the class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of a Personal Website and my Struggle to Find the Right One</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/swiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/swiss/</guid>
      <description>As a test manager, I understand the value of having a personal portfolio website to showcase my skills and experience. However, the process of creating a website that I was truly happy with took me 15 years and 18 different versions. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my journey and the lessons I&amp;rsquo;ve learned about the importance of a personal website and the struggle to find the right technology.&#xA;The Struggle to Find the Right Technology One of the biggest challenges I faced was finding the right technology to build my website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGR: An Experience</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/dgr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:13:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/dgr/</guid>
      <description>Every year, the Gentleman&amp;rsquo;s Ride holds a special place in my heart and my life. This year marks my sixth participation in this iconic event, and I&amp;rsquo;m more excited than ever to share what it represents to me, the causes it fights for, and why it&amp;rsquo;s so special.&#xA;The Gentleman&amp;rsquo;s Ride is more than just a motorcycle ride. It&amp;rsquo;s a global initiative aimed at raising awareness and funds for prostate cancer research and men&amp;rsquo;s mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I ditched Google Chrome, And why you should too.</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/arc/</guid>
      <description>Embracing a New Chapter: My Transition from Chrome to Arc Browser At the end of 2022, while reading about self-driving cars, my phone rang. It was a buddy excited about manned missions to Mars. As I glanced at my Mac and opened Chrome to learn more, I realized: everything around us is evolving rapidly, except our web browsers. They’ve remained almost the same for ages.&#xA;That was the moment I decided to change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Curiosity to Quality</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/posts/qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:13:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/posts/qa/</guid>
      <description>Although nowadays, careers related to computer science are highly sought after, I must admit that it was not at all my initial ambition. Yet, the winding path that led me to become a software tester is a beautiful testament to the power of curiosity and perseverance.&#xA;From a very young age, I have always been a passionate and curious child about everything. Each new toy quickly became an object of thorough investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nathan.swiss/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nathan.swiss/about/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: i test stuff. Based in Lausanne 🇨🇭, as a Test Manager, my role is to ensure that websites and applications function as they should. With over 8 years of experience in the QA field, I am known for being open, a bit crazy, and efficient in my work.&#xA;I am a trained IT management technician who has turned my passion into my profession: I do what I love and love what I do.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
